Hello Hello Friends, today I am going to tell you
how to get health insurance from SBI,
so first you login to the CSC portal,
after logging in,
instead of SBI search,
click on Motor Corporation Sewerage at the bottom, or
after clicking, you again log in to the
SBI General Insurance portal by entering the CSC ID and password,
this login will be done by
entering the CSC ID and password,
after logging in, now here I am
clicking on Health, after clicking on Mahal,
click on the rest,
after clicking on the previous one, you have to select the gender here, if
found then enter Male,
tap Female or Female, in Occupations, whoever is doing
whatever work, you can enter Bhaiya, you can
select this business or he,
after this you have to select the date of birth here, the
date of birth of the customer for whom you are doing, the date of birth on the certificate Aadhar
card, select that date of birth,
select the date of birth from whatever proof is there, after selecting the date of birth
Through this, select the date of birth,
after this select the selfie, just select the selfie,
after clicking on the bracelet, scroll down, after scrolling down, click on submit, after
submitting, click on this plant,
click on go and here we will
put the Nokia trick, we will rebel on all of them, scroll
down from the bottom and note it here also,
after clicking on 9, click
on continue, click on continue, after this let's
reduce the annual premium by some rupees 4000, from here, we will
click on the top here and move down further
here, click down
or click on Twitter,
now you see this, now the annual premium has reduced to
₹ 2000 and again
click on continue here,
after entering the first name last name, if there is a PAN number then
enter the PAN number, then after this,
enter the mobile number here, enter the mobile number of the customer
and enter the email ID
and after entering the email ID,
fill the address below, fill the address,
after this click on continue on both the sides here
After clicking on continue, here you have to enter the name of the nominee
whose name you give to the Navami,
then let's enter the name here,
enter the first name and last name,
after entering the first name and last name, you have to
select stop, you have to
enter the reaction with it normally and
click on next, click on next,
here you
click on selective payment, click on this electronic CSC
payment,
after clicking on maximum, now enter the user ID
and password here and click on payment,
after the payment is done,
download the policy, download it and
give it to the customer, see we have downloaded it
fully and by clicking on from here we make the office
ok, thank you friends, if you
liked our video then please like and subscribe